Guide to the Human Services Workshop records,1968-1993.
Human Services Workshop records, 1968-1993
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Human services workshop records, 1968-1993.
23-5-2873
Ronald B., House
1 cubic ft.
Manuals
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Human services, management, and personnel workshop records for programs held in Cornell's School of Industrial and Labor Relations and the New York State College of Human Ecology; workshops were in part sponsored by the United States Dept. of Education Rehabilitation Services Administration.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Human services, management, and personnel workshop records for programs held in Cornell's School of Industrial and Labor Relations and the New York State College of Human Ecology; workshops were in part sponsored by the United States Dept. of Education Rehabilitation Services Administration.
SUBJECTS
Names:
House, Ronald B.,; New York State College of Human Ecology.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; United States.Dept. of Education.Rehabilitation Services Administration.
Subjects:
Human services.; Management--Study and teaching.; Personnel management.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Contents
  - Cornell Workshop: Management Training Simulation - Player Manual, June 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Workshop: Management Training Simulation - Umpire Instructions, July 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Workshop: Professional and Management Training Simulation - Participant Manual (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Workshop: Staff Development Simulation - Participant Manual, Nov. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Workshop: Staff Development Simulation - Coordinator Work Folder and Instructions, Jan. 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Manpower - Rehabilitation Facility Simulation - Coordinator Instructions, July 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Manpower - Participant Manual, July 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pre-Simulation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Month One - Simulation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Month Two - Simulation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Month Three - Simulation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Month Four - Simulation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Months Five and Six - Simulation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Participant Manual, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Coordinator Pre-Game, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Coordinator Quarter 1, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Coordinator Quarter 2, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Coordinator Quarters 3 and 4, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Community-Based Placement Approaches - Agenda, Day 1, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Community-Based Placement Approaches - Day 2, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Community-Based Placement Approaches - Day 3, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Community-Based Placement Approaches - Days 4 and 5, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Supervisory Management - Agenda, Sections I & II, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Supervisory Management - Agenda, Sections III, IV & V, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Profitability and Program Management in Supported Employment, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Agenda, Pre-Game Coordinator - Quarter 1, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Coordinator, Quarters 2 and 3, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Community Residence Management Simulation - Quarter 4, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Personnel Management Wage and Salary Administration - Agenda, Wage Administration, Job Analysis, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Personnel Management Wage and Salary Administration - Job Evaluation, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Personnel Management Wage and Salary Administration, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Materials and Inventory Management, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Financial Management for Not-for-Profit Organizations, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Financial Management for Not-for-Profit Organizations, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Independent Living Management Simulation - Coordinator's Manual (file returned to Ron House), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Independent Living Management Simulation (file returned to Ron House), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Independent Living Fundraising and Development (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Independent Living Fundraising and Development, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Independent Living Fundraising and Development, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Supported Employment Management Simulation, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Supported Employment Management Simulation, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - An Introduction to Person Centered Planning and Implications for Organizational Change: Reconceptualizing the Community/Residence Model, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - An Introduction to Person Centered Planning and Implications for Organizational Change: Reconceptualizing the Community/Residence Model, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Human Service Administration Program - Transfer of program from I.L.R. School, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 45)